The heist begins at 40,000 ft.
Lift is a action, comedy, crime film directed by F. Gary Gray.
An international heist crew, led by Cyrus Whitaker, race to lift $500
million in gold from a passenger plane at 40,000 feet.
Cyrus Whitaker, played by Kevin Hart.
Abby Gladwell, played by Gugu Mbatha-Raw.
Dennis Huxley, played by Sam Worthington.
Denton, played by Vincent D'Onofrio.
Camila, played by Úrsula Corberó.
Lars Jorgensen, played by Jean Reno.
Lift is a 2024 American heist comedy film directed by F.
Gary Gray and written by Daniel Kunka.
The film stars Kevin Hart (who was also a producer), Gugu Mbatha-Raw, Vincent D'Onofrio,
Úrsula Corberó, Billy Magnussen, Jacob Batalon, Jean Reno, and Sam Worthington.
The plot follows an international thief and his crew who team up with an Interpol agent to
steal half a billion dollars' worth of gold bullion aboard a passenger flight.
Lift was released on Netflix on January 12, 2024.
The film explores themes of gold, airplane, gang of
thieves, heist, airplane hijacking.
The tone is lighthearted.